#### Contact

sathishkumar9919@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ sathishkumar6 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
After Effects
HTML5
Design

# Sathish Kumar\_S

Graphic Designer | Freelancer

Karaikkudi, Tamil Nadu, India

## Summary

Experienced Graphic Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the online media industry. Skilled in Adobe Photoshop, Design, Graphics, Social Work, and Graphic Design. Strong arts and design professional with a Bachelor of Computer Science focused in Computer Science from Alagappa University.

## Experience

Freelance

Freelance Graphic Designer September 2021 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Karaikkudi, Tamil Nadu, India

#### Aieraadvert

1 Year Experience as Creative Graphic Designer June 2021 - June 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Karaikkudi, Tamil Nadu, India

### Education

Alagappa University

Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer Science (October 2021 - 2024)

Maharishi vidya mandir Hr.sec.school karaikudi

Sahayamatha matriculationhr.sec School